[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A Grasshopper is characterized by its soft color and taste, which comes from this strong green liqueur.", "correct_answer": "Creme de Menthe", "incorrect_answers": ["Apple Pucker", "Creme de Grasshopper", "Lime Juice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which country was Carlos Mencia born?", "correct_answer": "Honduras", "incorrect_answers": ["Guatemala", "Ecuador", "Nicaragua"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the second book of the Bible?", "correct_answer": "Exodus", "incorrect_answers": ["Acts", "Mark", "Joshua"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Newsweeks unsuccessful sports publication?", "correct_answer": "Inside Sports", "incorrect_answers": ["Sports Newsweek", "The Week in Sports", "Sports Weekly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie was nominated in eight categories at the 72nd Academy Awards 2000?", "correct_answer": "American Beauty", "incorrect_answers": ["The Sixth Sense", "Magnolia", "The Green Mile"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these was not included in the 1940 Walt Disney animated movie Fantasia?", "correct_answer": "Dialogue", "incorrect_answers": ["Music", "Well-known Disney characters", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "ICQ is a type of what?", "correct_answer": "An instant messaging computer program", "incorrect_answers": ["ISP", "Bulletin Board", "Intelligence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A war, which was condemned by the United Nations, was fought in 1982 over a group of islands between which two countries?", "correct_answer": "Argentina and Great Britain", "incorrect_answers": ["Grenada and the USA", "Panama and the USA", "Chile and Argentina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the card game gin rummy, it is sometimes necessary to break a meld in order to keep your opponent from winning the hand.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the 2002 science fiction film Signs?", "correct_answer": "M. Night Shyamalan", "incorrect_answers": ["Tim Burton", "The Wachowski Brothers", "Stephen Spielberg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This weekly series was about a benevolent uncle and his niece Penny. He zoomed around in a small plane rounding up the rustlers and all the bad men.", "correct_answer": "Sky King", "incorrect_answers": ["King for a Day", "Mile High Ranch", "King of the Sky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Only three groups of land creatures get cavities - humans, pets kept by humans, and this group.", "correct_answer": "Bears", "incorrect_answers": ["Rodents", "Tigers", "Armadillos"]}]